<?xml version="1.0" encoding="Windows-1252" ?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
<MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
    <MASTER_PAD_VERSION>1.15</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
    <MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD for short, is a data set that is used by shareware authors to disseminate information to anyone interested in their software products. To find out more go to http://www.asp-shareware.org/pad</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
</MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
<Company_Info>
        <Company_Name>Sendero Software</Company_Name>
        <Address_1>9337-B Katy Freeway</Address_1>
        <Address_2>Suite 378</Address_2>
        <City_Town>Houston</City_Town>
        <State_Province>Tx</State_Province>
        <Zip_Postal_Code>77024</Zip_Postal_Code>
        <Country>USA</Country>
        <Company_WebSite_URL>http://www.senderosoftware.com</Company_WebSite_URL>
<Contact_Info>
        <Author_First_Name>Scott</Author_First_Name>
        <Author_Last_Name>Martin</Author_Last_Name>
        <Author_Email>smartin@senderosoftware.com</Author_Email>
        <Contact_First_Name>Bill</Contact_First_Name>
        <Contact_Last_Name>Gunn</Contact_Last_Name>
        <Contact_Email>bgunn@senderosoftware.com</Contact_Email>
    </Contact_Info>
<Support_Info>
        <Sales_Email>sales@senderosoftware.com</Sales_Email>
        <Support_Email>support@senderosoftware.com</Support_Email>
        <General_Email>info@senderosoftware.com</General_Email>
        <Sales_Phone>281-971-4013</Sales_Phone>
        <Support_Phone>281-971-4013</Support_Phone>
        <General_Phone>281-971-4013</General_Phone>
        <Fax_Phone>281-971-4013</Fax_Phone>
    </Support_Info>
</Company_Info>
<Program_Info>
        <Program_Name>DBF-Desktop</Program_Name>
        <Program_Version>1.01</Program_Version>
        <Program_Release_Month>09</Program_Release_Month>
        <Program_Release_Day>10</Program_Release_Day>
        <Program_Release_Year>2002</Program_Release_Year>
        <Program_Cost_Dollars>39.00</Program_Cost_Dollars>
        <Program_Cost_Other_Code />
        <Program_Cost_Other />
        <Program_Type>Shareware</Program_Type>
        <Program_Release_Status>Major Update</Program_Release_Status>
        <Program_Install_Support>Install and Uninstall</Program_Install_Support>
        <Program_OS_Support>Win95,Win98,WinME,WinNT 4.x,WinXP,Windows2000</Program_OS_Support>
        <Program_Language>English,Spanish,French,German,Italian</Program_Language>
<File_Info>
        <Filename_Versioned>DBFDk101.exe</Filename_Versioned>
        <Filename_Previous />
        <Filename_Generic>DBFDk.exe</Filename_Generic>
        <Filename_Long>DBFD-Trial-Setup.exe</Filename_Long>
        <File_Size_Bytes>6162373</File_Size_Bytes>
        <File_Size_K>6018</File_Size_K>
        <File_Size_MB>6.02</File_Size_MB>
    </File_Info>
<Expire_Info>
        <Has_Expire_Info>Y</Has_Expire_Info>
        <Expire_Count>30</Expire_Count>
        <Expire_Based_On>Days</Expire_Based_On>
        <Expire_Other_Info>30 Day Trial</Expire_Other_Info>
        <Expire_Month />
        <Expire_Day />
        <Expire_Year />
    </Expire_Info>
        <Program_Change_Info>International Support, Dot Prompt, Blob Images, Scripter Enhanced (CodeSite Support,Templates,Code Complete) Layout Manager, License Server</Program_Change_Info>
        <Program_Specific_Category>Development Tools</Program_Specific_Category>
        <Program_Categories>Database Management</Program_Categories>
        <Program_System_Requirements>32MB, 15MB HD</Program_System_Requirements>
        <Includes_JAVA_VM>N</Includes_JAVA_VM>
        <Includes_VB_Runtime>N</Includes_VB_Runtime>
        <Includes_DirectX>N</Includes_DirectX>
</Program_Info>
<Program_Descriptions>
<English>
        <Keywords>DBF,Desktop,Database,Manager,Apollo,SQL,ADS,Server,Sendero,xBase,DBase,Clipper,Hiper,CDX,FPT,NTX,NSX,Script</Keywords>
        <Char_Desc_45>DBF Database Manager</Char_Desc_45>
        <Char_Desc_80>DBF Database Manager for managing DBF files such as Fox,Clipper and Hiper-Six</Char_Desc_80>
        <Char_Desc_250>DBF Database Manager for managing DBF files such as Fox,Clipper and Hiper-Six</Char_Desc_250>
        <Char_Desc_450>DBF-Desktop Professional is the premier Database Manager for managing DBF files, providing the ability to create, modify and manage every aspect of your DBF file. Since DBF-Desktop was created using Apollo, we also support all features that are provided with Apollo, such as Clipper, FoxPro, and HiPer-6 tables along with advanced support for Apollo Database Server.</Char_Desc_450>
        <Char_Desc_2000>DBF-Desktop Professional is the premier Database Manager for managing DBF files, providing the ability to create, modify and manage every aspect of your DBF file. Since DBF-Desktop was created using Apollo, we also support all features that are provided with Apollo, such as Clipper, FoxPro, and HiPer-6 tables along with advanced support for Apollo Database Server.

International Support
Project Manager
Interactive Pascal Scripter (supports call to CodeSite from Raize.com)
Local SQL Builder
Dot Prompt support (50+ Commands)
Open Multiple Tables
Support for viewing blob images (BMP,JPG,ICO,GIF,RTF)
Script Editor supports Code Completion, Templates, Custom scripts included
File Editor (includes auto extension support)
Layout Manager for creating custom views
Custom Report Designer
Compare Structures/Directories
Connect to ADS from Apollo
Print grid directly to printer
Import/Export
License Server added to support concurrent license usage
plus many more ...</Char_Desc_2000>
</English>
</Program_Descriptions>
<Web_Info>
<Application_URLs>
        <Application_Info_URL>http://www.senderosoftware.com</Application_Info_URL>
        <Application_Order_URL>http://www.senderosoftware.com/index.asp?a=products&amp;pid=1&amp;tfi=Pricing</Application_Order_URL>
        <Application_Screenshot_URL>http://www.senderosoftware.com/_Images/Products/DBFd-Screenshots/FieldGroup.jpg</Application_Screenshot_URL>
        <Application_Icon_URL>http://www.senderosoftware.com/dbfdesktop/dbfdesktop.gif</Application_Icon_URL>
        <Application_XML_File_URL>http://www.senderosoftware.com/dbfdesktop/dbfdesktop.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
    </Application_URLs>
<Download_URLs>
        <Primary_Download_URL>http://www.senderosoftware.com/dbfdesktop/trial/dbfd-trial-setup.exe</Primary_Download_URL>
        <Secondary_Download_URL />
        <Additional_Download_URL_1 />
        <Additional_Download_URL_2 />
    </Download_URLs>
</Web_Info>
<Permissions>
        <Distribution_Permissions>==============

NOTICE

The installation executable of DBF-Desktop (&quot;SOFTWARE&quot;) 
is provided to YOU by Sendero Software, LLC (&quot;LICENSOR&quot;) for 
distribution only under the following terms.  LICENSOR reserves all rights 
not expressly granted to YOU.  LICENSOR retains ownership of all copies of 
the SOFTWARE itself.  YOU assume sole responsibility for YOUR distribution 
of the SOFTWARE.

PLEASE READ THIS DOCUMENT CAREFULLY.  THE INDIVIDUAL OR ENTITY INTENDING TO 
DISTRIBUTE THIS SOFTWARE (&quot;YOU&quot;) AGREES TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS OF THIS 
DISTRIBUTION LICENSE.  IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS 
DISTRIBUTION LICENSE, YOU ARE PROHIBITED FROM DISTRIBUTING THIS SOFTWARE.

1. OWNERSHIP

This SOFTWARE and the related copyrights and intellectual property rights, 
are the exclusive property of Sendero Software, LLC and/or its 
suppliers.  YOU acquire no title, right or interest in the SOFTWARE other 
than the DISTRIBUTION LICENSE rights granted herein.

2. DISTRIBUTION LICENSE

YOU are granted a limited, non-exclusive, revokable DISTRIBUTION LICENSE to 
do only the following:

Make complete and unmodified copies of only the installation executable of 
the TRIAL version of this SOFTWARE as released on the website(s) of 
Sendero Software, LLC, in machine-readable form for distribution to a 
third party solely for the purpose of evaluation for purchase by the third 
party, provided the entire contents of the TRIAL version are copied in 
their entirety with payment, copyright, and trademark information in place.  
Although the SOFTWARE may not be sold, a distribution fee may be charged 
for the service of providing this SOFTWARE to others on physical, CD-ROM or 
magnetic media (i.e. charging for the media and duplication services only).  
This SOFTWARE is protected under United States copyright laws and 
international treaty provisions.  This SOFTWARE and documentation is 
Copyright (c) 2003 by Sendero Software, LLC. All Rights Reserved 
Worldwide.

YOU AGREE THAT YOU SHALL NOT DISTRIBUTE A REGISTERED VERSION OF THIS 
SOFTWARE NOR SHALL YOU DISTRIBUTE ANY REGISTRATION CODE FOR THIS SOFTWARE.

You agree that you shall only distribute the SOFTWARE in a manner that 
complies with all applicable laws in the jurisdiction(s) in which you 
distribute the SOFTWARE, including, but not limited to, applicable 
restrictions concerning copyright and other intellectual property rights.

3. RESTRICTIONS

YOU shall not remove from the SOFTWARE any trademark, tradename, copyright 
notice or other notice, and shall be responsible for their preservation on 
the copies received hereunder and for their reproduction on any backup copy 
of the SOFTWARE or on any portion of the SOFTWARE merged into other 
programs or SITES.

YOU may NOT sublicense, or assign copies of the SOFTWARE to others.  The 
SOFTWARE contains trade secrets.  YOU may NOT decompile, reverse engineer, 
disassemble, or otherwise reduce the SOFTWARE to a human readable form.  
YOU MAY NOT MODIFY, ADAPT, TRANSLATE, RENT, LEASE, LOAN, RESELL FOR PROFIT, 
OR OTHERWISE ASSIGN OR TRANSFER THE SOFTWARE, OR CREATE DERIVATIVE WORKS 
BASED UPON THE SOFTWARE OR ANY PART THEREOF without the prior written 
consent of Sendero Software, LLC.

4. PROTECTION AND SECURITY.

YOU agree to use YOUR best efforts and to take all reasonable steps to 
safeguard the SOFTWARE to ensure that no unauthorized person shall have 
access thereto and that no unauthorized copy, publication, disclosure or 
distribution in whole or in part, in any form, shall be made.  YOU 
acknowledge that the SOFTWARE contains valuable confidential information 
and trade secrets and that unauthorized use and/or copying are harmful to 
LICENSOR.

5. TERMINATION.

a)  This DISTRIBUTION LICENSE is effective until terminated.  This 
DISTRIBUTION LICENSE will terminate immediately without notice from 
LICENSOR if YOU fail to comply with any of its provisions.  LICENSOR may 
immediately revoke and terminate the license granted hereunder by providing 
written notice to YOU if any of the following events occur:  breach by YOU 
of any provisions of this DISTRIBUTION LICENSE.

b)  Upon termination of the DISTRIBUTION LICENSE granted hereunder, 
LICENSOR reserves the right to take any legal action necessary to recover 
any damages incurred by LICENSOR.

6. PRINT MEDIA PUBLISHERS

Print media publishers wishing to distribute this SOFTWARE on CD-ROM or 
magnetic media in combination of a book must agree to all terms of this 
DISTRIBUTION LICENSE and, additionally, must provide a copy of the book/CD-
ROM combination to Sendero Software, LLC, 9337-B Katy Freeway #378, 
Houston, Tx 77024 USA

7. GENERAL.

This DISTRIBUTION LICENSE will be governed by and construed in accordance 
with the laws of the State of Texas, USA, and shall inure to the 
benefit of LICENSOR and YOU and their successors, assigns and legal 
representatives.  If any provision of this DISTRIBUTION LICENSE is held by 
a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid or unenforceable to any 
extent under applicable law, that provision will be enforced to the maximum 
extent permissible, and the remaining provisions of this License will 
remain in full force and effect.  Any notices or other communications to be 
sent to LICENSOR must be mailed first class, postage prepaid, to the 
following address: Sendero Software, LLC, 9337-B Katy Freeway #378, 
Houston, Tx 77024 USA. 

This Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between the parties with 
respect to the subject matter hereof, and all prior proposals, agreements, 
representations, statements and undertakings are hereby expressly cancelled 
and superseded.  This Agreement may not be changed or amended except by a 
written instrument executed by a duly authorized officer of LICENSOR.

8. ACKNOWLEDGEMENT.

BY DISTRIBUTING THIS SOFTWARE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ THIS 
DISTRIBUTION LICENSE, UNDERSTAND IT, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY ITS TERMS AND 
CONDITIONS.  Should YOU have any questions concerning this DISTRIBUTION 
LICENSE, contact LICENSOR at the address set forth above.

Copyright (c) 2003 by Sendero Software, LLC.
All Rights Reserved Worldwide.</Distribution_Permissions>
        <EULA>License Agreement
-----------------
You should carefully read the following terms and conditions
before  using  the software.  By  using  this  software  you
indicate that you accept the present license agreement.

DISCLAIMER
----------
This software is provided on an  &quot;as is&quot;  basis without war-
ranty of any kind,  expressed or implied,  including but not
limited  to  the implied warranties  of merchantability  and
fitness for a particular purpose. The person using the soft-
ware bears all risk as to the quality and performance of the
software.  The author  will not be liable  for  any special,
incidental,  consequential,  indirect or similar damages due
to loss of data  or  any other reason, even if the author or
an agent of the author  has been advised  of the possibility
of such damages.  In no event shall  the author's  liability
for any damages  ever exceed the price  paid for the license
to use the software, regardless of the form of the claim.

Restrictions
------------
You may not use, copy, modify, translate, or transfer the
programs, documentation, or any copy except as expressly
defined in this agreement. You may not attempt to unlock
or bypass any &quot;copy-protection&quot; or authentication algorithm
utilized by the program.

You may not remove or modify any copyright notice or the
method by which it may be invoked.

Operating license
-----------------
You have the non-exclusive right to use any enclosed
program only by a single person, on a single computer at
a time. You may physically transfer the program from one
computer to another, provided that the program is used
only by a single person, on a single computer at a time.
In group projects where multiple persons will use the
program, you must purchase an individual license for
each member of the group. Use over a &quot;local area network&quot;
(within the same locale) is permitted provided that the
program is used only by a single person, on a single
computer at a time. Use over a &quot;wide area network&quot;
(outside the same locale) is strictly prohibited under any
and all circumstances.</EULA>
</Permissions>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>
